Local 1199 Additional Files 5525
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Westside Rehabilitation Center (Box 100, Folder 24)
- Yonkers Hamilton Sanitorium, Inc. (Box 100, Folder 25)
- Delegates Newsletter (Hospital Division), 1973-1974 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- What's On At 1199, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- What's On At 1199, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 3)